[Music]
[音乐]
okay I think it's about time to start so
好吧，我认为是时候开始了，所以
hello everyone welcome to my talk cloud
大家好，欢迎来到我的演讲云
native spring good admin and at first
本地春季良好管理员，起初
I'd like to apologize for the sketchy
我想为粗略的道歉
bus were the title and after looking at
公共汽车是标题，看了之后
all the cloud vendors and thinking about
所有云供应商和思考
it which when I should show I would say
我应该在什么时候告诉我
okay I was thinking okay what's the
好吧，我在想好吧，那是什么
common denominator today with all the
今天所有的共同点
cloud vendors and most of the cloud
云供应商和大多数云
vendors are offering some kubernetes
供应商提供了一些kubernetes
cluster or managed communities or even
集群或托管社区，甚至
if you're doing your private cloud or
如果您正在使用私有云或
something like that
这样的东西
mostly you will use communities so maybe
大多数情况下，您将使用社区，所以也许
the title should be spin with admin on
标题应与admin一起旋转
community so that's what we are going to
社区，这就是我们要去的地方
see in the next 45 minutes I guess we
在接下来的45分钟内看到
have some minutes left in the end for
最后还有几分钟
questions and yeah you will learn a lot
问题，是的，您会学到很多
about Springwood admin the tool itself
关于Springwood管理工具本身
and you might learn something about
你可能会学到一些关于
spring flower to give anita's the new
春天的花朵给安妮塔的新
kits on the spring cloud block and yeah
春天的云块上的工具包，是的
I would show how you can use the
我会告诉你如何使用
discovery from spring cloud communities
从春季云社区中发现
with spring with admin first I'd like to
首先要与春季管理员一起
introduce myself I'm Your Highness I'm
介绍自己，我是Your下，我是
from Germany as you most probably
最有可能来自德国
probably can tell from my heavy accent
从我的重音中可以看出
I'm working for concentric a consultancy
我在同心咨询公司工作
company from Germany and I'm the
公司来自德国，我是
maintainer of the spring wood admin
Spring 木管理员的维护者
project the project itself is about four
项目项目本身大约是四个
and a half years old
半岁
we have over seventeen thousand stars on
我们有超过一万七千颗恒星
github and it's apache license so you
github和它的apache许可证，所以你
can use it for free we don't earn any
可以免费使用我们没有任何收入
money with it it's all for fame and
赚钱都是为了名利
glory and the thing why I can do this is
荣耀，而我之所以能做到这一点是
my company allows me to work twenty
我的公司允许我工作二十
percent of my
我的百分比
work time on this project or anything
这个项目的工作时间或其他
else I like so some colleagues are
否则我喜欢，所以有些同事
looking into machine learning some
看着机器学习一些
others into other weird
别人变成别的怪
fancies AI stuff and such things or
幻想AI东西之类的东西，或者
blockchain or whatever and I'm doing the
区块链之类的东西，我正在做
admin project but I can tell you one day
管理项目，但有一天我可以告诉你
a week is by far not enough so I also
一个星期远远不够，所以我也
invest a lot of my private time and we
花很多我的私人时间，我们
have to first way we need a application
必须首先需要我们的应用程序
we'd like to monitor and maybe you solve
我们想监控一下，也许您可​​以解决
the talk from my colleague Benjamin
我的同事本杰明的讲话
yesterday about causing chaos
昨天关于造成混乱
engineering I just ripped his
我刚撕开他的工程
application so maybe this light looks
应用程序，所以也许这盏灯看起来
familiar
熟悉的
we have just been good application using
我们一直在使用
sprinkler gateway in front to which just
前面的自动喷水灭火网关
have some rest endpoints and which talks
有一些休息的端点，哪个会说话
to the spin boot application will be
旋转启动应用程序将
back which also replicated we have
后面也复制了我们
multiple ports it's really just a bit of
多个端口，实际上只是
rest yeah I guess Benjamin and me was
休息吧，我想本杰明和我是
too lazy to write some nice UI what this
懒得写一些漂亮的UI这是什么
example and yeah we have an ingress in
是的，是的，我们有一个入口
front to access all the things and now I
前面访问所有的东西，现在我
will show you how we can monitor this
将向您展示我们如何进行监控
application without touching the code of
无需触摸代码的应用程序
it and we we even don't need to build a
它，我们甚至不需要建立一个
new container images for this
为此的新容器图像
application we have some requirements
应用我们有一些要求
for the applications to be monitored we
对于要监视的应用程序，我们
have to use the Springwood activator so
必须使用Springwood活化剂
but if you're using communities you most
但是如果您使用社区，那么您最多
probably have it already included for
可能已经包含了
the eliteness and readiness probes and
精英和战备调查
also the activator endpoints have to be
激活器端点也必须是
exposed by HTTP and let's say if you
通过HTTP公开，假设您
have a simple message queue worker or
有一个简单的消息队列工作者或
something like that and
像这样的东西
have a sublet engine orinary included
包含转租引擎
you can monitor it currently with spring
您现在可以在春季监控它
with admin so at one company we just
与管理员，所以在一家公司，我们只是
have Tomcat included and some batch
包含Tomcat和一些批处理
processes and just for the sake of
流程，只是为了
monitoring these things okay next I'll
监视这些东西好吧，我接下来
show you how to set up the Springwood
向您展示如何设置Springwood
admin and the easiest thing would be to
管理员，最简单的事情是
go on the start of spring IO I think
我认为春季IO开始
since 101 one year or one and a half
自101年以来一年半
we're integrated into the pyramid and
我们已经融入金字塔
into the spring initializer so you can
进入Spring 初始值设定项，以便您可以
easily generate a project from there the
轻松地从那里生成一个项目
downside as we want to use Kevin looters
缺点，因为我们要使用凯文掠夺者
it's currently not available
目前不可用
I hope they will make it soon into the
我希望他们能尽快进入
initializer but yeah you have to do it
初始值设定项，但是是的，您必须这样做
by hand I prepared a little bit for that
用手我为此做了一点准备
so I'm not going to bore you with
所以我不会厌烦你
writing docker files and such for the
编写docker文件等
admin server itself you just need to
管理服务器本身，您只需要
include this room would admin start a
包括这个房间将管理员开始
server which will pull in some Java
服务器将拉入一些Java
files containing the UI for Springwood
包含Springwood用户界面的文件
admin and the rest endpoints and we also
管理员和其他端点，我们也
separated a bit of the spring cloud
分开了一点Spring Cloud
dependent stuff and the recent times we
依赖的东西和最近的时代
had some releases which didn't support
有一些不支持的版本
any spring cloud stuff and because they
任何春天的云东西，因为他们
weren't ready yet I hope we will not
还没准备好我希望我们不会
experience that anymore but yeah we will
经历了，但是是的，我们会
time will tell also we need the spring
时间会告诉我们我们需要春天
cloud key Bonita starter
云密钥Bonita入门
which ships the discovery client for
运送发现客户端的
sprinklers cuban eaters and
洒水器古巴食者和
[Music]
[音乐]
we have no versions here we have for
我们这里没有版本
spring cloud a bomb we are going to
春天的云，我们要炸弹
import and we also provide a bomb for as
进口，我们还为
you spin wood upon so yeah it's it's
你在上面旋转木头，是的，是
like yeah I hope you're used to spring
就像是的，我希望你习惯春天
cloud anyone using spring cloud already
已经使用Spring Cloud覆盖了任何人
okay what are using Eureka or a shouted
好吧，正在使用尤里卡或大喊
conflict manager okay yeah okay now we
冲突经理好吧，好吧，现在我们
have our dependencies in place we and we
有我们的依赖我们和我们
just need to do some configuration on
只需要在上做一些配置
our application class first we have to
首先我们的应用程序类
enable admin server which is going to
启用将要运行的管理服务器
instantiate some spin boot
实例化一些旋转启动
configurations with all the controller
所有控制器的配置
staff and background tasks for checking
人员和后台任务进行检查
health s-sarah we have to use the add
健康s-sarah我们必须使用添加
enable discovery client so the cabinet
启用发现客户端，以便机柜
is discovery client gets included and it
发现客户端被包括在内并且它
was until yesterday in northern the docs
直到昨天北部的文档
but the issue has been closed yesterday
但问题已于昨天关闭
we have to enable scheduling because is
我们必须启用调度，因为
the spring cloud kubernetes client has a
Spring Cloud Kubernetes客户端有一个
scheduled tasks for watching the changes
安排任务以观察更改
of services endpoints and ports and if
服务端点和端口以及
we forget that we will see services but
我们忘记了我们会看到服务，但是
they won't get updated at the as they
他们不会在时更新
change or new comes up others go down so
变化或新事物出现，其他事物下降，因此
it's really important to use this we
使用这个非常重要
would be right to go and we could now
将是正确的，我们现在可以
spin
旋转
this app there's one trick you might
这个应用程式可能有一个技巧
have you might have some non spring
你可能有一些非春季
boots services on your on your cluster I
在您的群集上引导服务
don't know databases go along staff at
不知道数据库的工作人员
alone and if you just want to have these
一个人，如果你只是想拥有这些
spring good applications in your in your
在您的内部产生良好的应用程序
spin would admin you can use this Z
旋转将管理员，您可以使用此Z
servals
serv
labeled selector from the sprinkler
喷头上标记的选择器
Kevin it is client and it will only show
凯文，它是客户，只会显示
you the services
您的服务
TEKT was whistles label yes the other
TEKT是口哨标签，是另一个
thing I am going to explain there now we
我现在要在那里解释的事情
can spin this up
可以把它旋转起来
we have to wait a little bit to get
我们必须等待一点时间才能得到
those running yes and we would see the
那些是的，我们会看到
UI I forgot some little things as you
用户界面我忘了一些小事
know we are running on kubernetes the
知道我们在kubernetes上运行
admin application deploys like any other
管理应用程序像其他任何部署一样部署
Springwood application so if you're
Springwood应用程序，如果您
using venetus are using communities
使用venetus使用社区
short pants yeah okay so I don't have to
短裤，是的，所以我不必
explain that much we have a regular
解释很多，我们有定期
deployment with the image I pre-built
我预先构建的映像进行部署
this image and the important part is we
这个形象，重要的是我们
have to use a service account and the
必须使用服务帐户，并且
service account gets associated with a
服务帐户与
certain role and this role for the role
一定的角色，此角色为角色
based access and communities allows us
基于访问和社区允许我们
to get this and watch all the pod
得到这个，看所有的 bean 荚
services and endpoints this is also one
服务和端点这也是一个
thing currently missing in the
目前在
documentation of spring cloud
Spring Cloud的文档
communities and I only saw one example
社区，我只看到一个例子
listing all of the verbs and all of the
列出所有动词和所有
resources and yeah maybe you should go
资源，是的，也许你应该去
and try to figure out what you really
并弄清楚你到底是什么
need to use and that's the minimal list
需要使用，这是最小的清单
I'd come up with and so we just want to
我想出了，所以我们只想
read things we don't want to manipulate
阅读我们不想操纵的东西
any stuff and I've set up an ordinary
任何东西，我已经建立了一个普通的
service for this pyramid admin and some
这个金字塔管理员和一些服务
ingress so nothing special about that
进入所以没什么特别的
and yeah if you go on the UI we see the
是的，如果您进入用户界面，我们会看到
all applications we also provide a nice
所有应用程序我们还提供了一个不错的选择
ball body view if you want to
球体视图，如果你想
put a big screen on the on your wall in
在屏幕上放一个大屏幕
your office
你的办公室
yeah and I will just submit simulate
是的，我只会提交模拟
what's going going to happen if I take a
如果我拿了一个会发生什么
service down the spring would happen
春天会降职
regularly Paul's in the background and
经常有保罗在后台
now we see how to use yellow which means
现在我们知道如何使用黄色
restricted one of the instances has a
受限制的实例之一具有
problem so we see the application is
问题，所以我们看到该应用程序是
down I just switched we helped in the
下来，我刚刚切换，我们帮助了
background to out of service and what
停止服务的背景以及什么
should happen next earth that's yeah
应该发生在下一个地球上
it's now green the communities just
现在是绿色社区
killed the service and should a second
杀死了服务，应该再秒钟
one should spin up and a few seconds and
一个人应该旋转几秒钟，然后
show up also here in the dashboard we
也在我们的仪表板中显示
currently don't have any check for
目前没有任何检查
having at least certain instances of an
至少具有
application we might add this in the
应用程序，我们可以在
future I think it's really useful to to
未来，我认为这对
to check the minimal instances if I
检查最小实例，如果我
would run this on HTTP with TLS security
将在具有TLS安全性的HTTP上运行
I would have gotten notification yeah
我本来会通知的
because I'm just running plain HTTP we
因为我只是运行普通的HTTP
couldn't see that but I have also used
看不到，但我也用过
setup a man notification and just used a
设置一个人通知，只是使用一个
tests SMTP server mail hoc very nice
测试SMTP服务器邮件特别好
tool if you want to use some tests on
工具，如果您想使用一些测试
mailing and I've have a notification
邮寄，我已经收到通知
yeah your instance was going down and we
是的，您的实例正在下降，我们
also provide a plenty of other modifiers
还提供了很多其他修饰符
so slack Microsoft means whatever
如此懈怠的微软意味着什么
and most of the notifications are really
而且大多数通知是
easy to set up that for the male part I
容易为男性部分设置
just included the spring would start a
刚刚包括春天将开始
mail and then needed to tell where the
邮件，然后需要告诉在哪里
where the mail host of the the SMTP
SMTP的邮件主机
server is located and just an email
服务器位于，只有一封电子邮件
address and if something when goes wrong
地址，如果出问题了
you just getting notification
您刚刚收到通知
immediately but maybe you have some
立即，但也许你有一些
other alerting in place
其他警报到位
Springwood admin has a lot of different
Springwood管理员有很多不同之处
benefit and notifications if you're
福利和通知（如果您是
running a cluster maybe you should use a
运行集群，也许您应该使用
more professional solution yes now
更专业的解决方案
what's what you might have noticed is
您可能已经注意到的是
that I also show the version in the list
我也在列表中显示了版本
and this is not out of the box the spin
这不是开箱即用的
would happen itself takes the
会发生本身需要
information from the info endpoint and
来自信息端点的信息和
to have that included it's very easy you
包含其中很容易
need just to include the building for go
只需要包括要去的建筑物
for your Springwood maven plug-in and
为您的Springwood Maven插件和
when doing the build the goal will take
在进行构建时，目标将是
some informations from your build put it
来自您的构建的一些信息
in a built up properties file included
在包含的内置属性文件中
into your in your jar and that will be
放进你的罐子里，那将是
shipped with when requesting the info
请求信息时附带
endpoint and there is plug-in I think
端点，并且我认为有插件
it's called come get commit ID plugin
它叫做来获取提交ID插件
which is doing similar things but also
在做类似的事情，但也
includes the commit our tag over a
包括将我们的代码提交到
branch whatever information from your
分支您的任何信息
git and includes this into the and for
git并将其包含在和中
endpoint and if we are going to view
端点，如果我们要查看
some of the details I just
我只是一些细节
another one yeah you can also see what
是的，你也可以看到
the artifact what's what the description
工件是什么描述
or the name a group ID when was it built
或建立群组名称时的名称
but despite that we only see okay the
但是尽管如此，我们只能看到
instances up and nothing really so we
实例最多，实际上什么也没有，所以我们
just see on the left just the details
只是在左边看到的只是细节
and we have plenty more by default
默认情况下，我们还有更多
Springwood activator only exposed see
斯普林伍德活化剂只暴露见
the info and then the health endpoint
信息，然后是运行状况端点
and we really have plenty more
而且我们还有更多
[Music]
[音乐]
plenty more endpoints which you can
您可以使用更多的端点
visualize and screen would happen so you
可视化和屏幕会发生，所以你
just need to expose the endpoints and as
只需公开端点和
promised I won't touch the applications
保证我不会碰这些应用程序
so I just set my room variable with
所以我只是用
communities to do that so it's the
社区做到这一点，这是
exposed exposure include with a star I
暴露暴露包括一颗星我
just expose all of the endpoints if you
只要暴露所有端点
don't want that list them here so you
不想在这里列出他们，所以你
can exclude some of the endpoints
可以排除某些端点
Springwood admin will just hide the view
Springwood管理员只会隐藏视图
for that endpoints that will not lead to
对于那些不会导致
any errors but maybe you don't want to
任何错误，但也许您不想
export the full power and have the full
出口全部力量并拥有全部
responsibility for everything and we
对一切负责，我们
also expose the details from the health
也会暴露健康的细节
endpoint so we get the information for
端点，以便我们获取有关的信息
each of the health indicators and you
每个健康指标和您
have three options
有三个选择
never which is the default so you just
从不，这是默认设置，所以您只是
get the single up or you can use when
单身或者你可以在什么时候使用
authenticated currently I don't use any
目前已认证，我不使用任何
security authentication mechanism here I
我这里的安全认证机制
will come back to that later and I use
稍后会回来，我用
the option always so we
该选项始终如此，因此我们
always show all details now everything
现在总是显示所有细节
should have been redeployed and take
应该重新部署并采取
this one and how we see all the details
这个以及我们如何看待所有细节
of the health indicators we also support
我们还支持哪些健康指标
customer health indicators you should be
您应该是客户健康指标
everything here so in this application I
这里的一切，所以在此应用程序中，我
just included a data source which is an
只是包含一个数据源
SQL DB and Springwood activator
SQL DB和Springwood激活器
automatically set up the health
自动设置健康
indicator for that also what I think a
指标，这也是我认为的
nice shortcut is I have included the
不错的捷径是我已经将
swagger UI in this application but I
摇摇欲坠的用户界面，但我
don't want to memorize all the URLs for
不想记住所有的URL
my different application in the
我在
difference-maker your eyes and yeah so I
改变你的眼睛，是的，所以我
just included a property info dot
刚刚包含一个属性信息点
swagger UI and then an URL and it will
摇摇晃晃的用户界面，然后是一个网址，它将
get rendered as link so I just can click
被渲染为链接，所以我可以单击
on it
在上面
drum straight to it and I don't have to
直接鼓起来，我不必
memorize anything and also I could use
记住任何东西，我也可以使用
communities and some environment
社区和一些环境
variables to make this dynamic for each
变量使每个动态
of my environments or something okay
我的环境还是可以的
now yeah we just exposed all of the end
现在是的，我们只是暴露了所有的结局
points which is probably not what we
点可能不是我们
might want to do in production this is
可能想在生产中做的是
the normal ingress endpoint from my
来自我的正常入口端点
application and now I exposed everything
应用程序，现在我暴露了一切
to the outside world so please don't do
到外面的世界，所以请不要这样做
that
那
you could write some magic crazy ingress
你可以写一些神奇的疯狂入口
rules to block that path or you could
规则来阻止那条路，否则你可以
just change the port for the management
只需更改管理端口
server for the posi activator this is
Posi激活器的服务器，这是
what we're going to do next just started
我们接下来要做的只是开始
so we don't have to wait and for the
因此我们不必等待，
applications we just set the management
我们只设置应用程序的管理
server port 90-80 in this case and
在这种情况下，服务器端口为90-80，并且
expose it as container port so it will
将其暴露为容器端口，因此它将
be moved of the male port and we won't
被男性港口感动，我们不会
be accessible by our the my normal
我的正常人可以访问
ingress but somehow we need to tell the
进入，但我们需要以某种方式告诉
Springwood admin where to find the
Springwood管理员在哪里找到
activator endpoints so we added a new
激活剂端点，所以我们添加了一个新的
port to a service and call it management
移植到服务并称为管理
and then we have to tell the Springwood
然后我们要告诉斯普林伍德
admin or the discovery client client in
管理员或发现客户端客户端
particular please primary port name to
特别是请为主端口名称
use is management
用是管理
so these bring clouds kubernetes will go
所以这些带来了云Kubernetes会去
through the endpoint list of the through
通过的端点列表
the port list of of the pot and
锅的端口列表和
we'll use the one named management so
我们将使用一个命名管理
now we should get a not found yeah four
现在我们应该得到一个找不到四
octave way for the actuator path on our
执行器路径的八度音程
main ingress but the spring would happen
主要进入但春天会发生
still sees the end point and can access
仍然看到终点并可以访问
them a short recap yeah we added two
他们简短回顾是的，我们添加了两个
dependencies we enabled the admin server
依赖关系，我们启用了管理服务器
the discovery client and the scheduling
发现客户端和调度
yeah
是的
which I've not shown yeah we need a
我没有展示过，是的，我们需要一个
docker image we need a deployment a
docker image我们需要部署一个
service an ingress for admin and we have
为管理员服务，我们有
to setup the role based access control
设置基于角色的访问控制
for the admin I we can use yeah we we
对于管理员，我可以使用，是的，我们
have changed the management port that's
更改了管理端口
good I will talk about to look here in a
好，我会谈谈在这里
few seconds and we have the the custom
几秒钟，我们有自定义
links edit with the info properties and
链接使用信息属性进行编辑，并且
the external views I can short demo as
我可以简短演示的外部视图
you might have some others some other
你可能还有其他一些
applications like in graph Anna for
像图Anna这样的应用
metrics or a Cabana for locks you might
指标或小屋的锁，您可能会
want to have all your applications
想要拥有所有应用程序
tightly together you can with the new
您可以与新产品紧密结合
spin with admin version coming up at
与管理版本一起旋转
very easily a top level link right here
很容易在这里建立顶层链接
to to any you like you we also provide
对于您喜欢的任何人，我们还提供
an an option to embed it as an iframe so
一个将其嵌入为iframe的选项
you can keep things close together and
您可以使事情保持紧密联系
it's less URLs to memorize or your link
要记住的网址或链接更少
list will get sure yes
列表将确保是
now um this is how it's currently look
现在，这是目前的样子
it looks like we have the ingress for
看来我们有入口
the admin server the admin server that
管理服务器
serves X as a proxy to access the
以X作为代理访问
actuator endpoints so you really want to
执行器端点，所以您真的想
make the admin server secure and please
使管理服务器安全，请
maybe you shouldn't expose the admin
也许你不应该公开管理员
server on the web last week I just found
上周我在网上找到服务器
one unsecured admin server via Google
一台不安全的Google管理服务器
you can shut everything off so no good
你可以关闭所有东西，所以不好
idea yeah and the admin server itself
是的想法和管理服务器本身
talks to the kubernetes master or API to
与kubernetes管理员或API交谈
get the information for the pods and if
获取有关吊舱的信息，以及
we do a request from the UI it will be
我们从UI发出一个请求
proxied via the admin server and will
通过管理服务器代理，将
directly access via the activator
通过激活器直接访问
endpoints which leads me to the topic
端点引导我进入主题
security so we currently ship no default
安全性，因此我们目前没有默认发货
and I guess it will stay with that way
我想它将保持这种方式
as we have too many options you could do
因为我们可以选择的太多
none which is not really an option but
没有，这不是真正的选择，但
you can do a classical session based
你可以做一个经典的会议
approach using cookies we have an sample
使用cookie的方法，我们有一个示例
on that in our documentation typically
通常在我们的文档中
in the setup you authenticate on the
在设置中，您需要在
admin server and the admin server itself
管理服务器和管理服务器本身
uses a service account to access the the
使用服务帐户访问
actuator and ones in the back so the
执行器和后面的那个
decision whether the user can access the
决定用户是否可以访问
act endpoint is made by Springwood admin
行为端点由Springwood管理员制定
if you don't want to have it that way
如果你不想那样的话
you could use oauth2 and forward the
您可以使用oauth2并转发
tokens from the UI via the admin service
通过管理服务从用户界面获取令牌
to the real actuator and point in the
到真正的执行器并指向
back and then the application in the
返回，然后在
back could decide whether the users
后面可以决定用户是否
allowed or not
允许与否
to access the endpoint and you would
访问端点，您将
also need a second
还需要一秒钟
service account for the aplans server
aplans服务器的服务帐户
just to fetch the health information and
只是为了获取健康信息，
the background task so for the heads
负责人的后台任务
checking but you wouldn't give it any
检查，但你什么都不给
other permissions like setting lock
其他权限，例如设置锁定
levels or something
水平或东西
we're showing next we also have an
我们接下来要展示的是
example by my colleague Tomas who is
我的同事托马斯（Tomas）的例子
also giving a talk about Kiki Club today
今天也有关于琪琪俱乐部的演讲
I think and he written a blog post about
我想，他写了一篇有关
how to secure the spring would happen
如何确保Spring 会发生
with the whiskey o'clock so it's also
威士忌的时间也是如此
easy to set this up and yeah you could
易于设置，是的，您可以
use anything else bring security offers
使用其他任何东西带来安全保障
at Springwood
在斯普林伍德
admin at service just a spring boot
在服务管理员只是一个 spring boot
application so choose whatever fits best
应用程序，所以选择最合适的
okay okay now let's have a little tour
好吧好吧，现在让我们进行一些游览
through the endpoint for each
通过每个端点
application yeah I shot this page we
应用程序是的，我拍摄了此页面，我们
have the build information the health
具有构建信息的健康
information anything you put into the
信息，您放入
infor endpoint yeah that's the metadata
infor终结点是的，这就是元数据
provided via the discovery client
通过发现客户端提供
you could also we also see here the the
您也可以在这里看到
labor the labor types from boot you
从引导您开始工作
could so add anything from communities
可以从社区添加任何东西
you like I have we have some rough
你喜欢我有一些粗糙
metrics shown here we have also a metric
此处显示的指标我们还有一个指标
page which you could use to quickly see
您可以用来快速查看的页面
some numbers
一些数字
this just you know I don't know and show
这只是你知道我不知道和显示
the metric the thing is we don't resist
度量标准是我们不抗拒
any of this data
任何这些数据
we're just scraping the endpoints and
我们只是在刮擦端点，
looking at what's a good value what's
看什么是好的价值，什么是
the current value so if we switch views
当前值，所以如果我们切换视图
everything is lost and yeah maybe go for
一切都消失了，是的，也许
Prometheus or in flux to be and do
普罗米修斯或不断变化
something proficient if you if you are
如果你是精通的话
using a cloud environment and so yeah
使用云环境等等
it's mostly when I do with some local
主要是当我与一些当地人在一起时
things I just I have a quick look at
我只是快速浏览一下的东西
that
那
so I on my mini cube I don't know it
所以我在我的迷你立方体上不知道
need any Ravana or something like that
需要任何Ravana之类的东西
we show all the information from the
我们显示了来自
environment endpoint so we can see any
环境端点，所以我们可以看到任何
system property set any system
系统属性设置任何系统
environment variable set we also see the
环境变量集我们也看到了
contents of application properties or
应用程序属性的内容或
Yama or whatever you use also with the
Yama或您在
location where the setting is made and
进行设置的位置以及
if you have multiple settings with the
如果您有多个设置
same key it will read from top to bottom
从上到下读取相同的键
so the most top one is the active one
所以最顶级的是活跃的
it's just the data we get from the
只是我们从
environment end point and that thinks
环境终点，并认为
this is one of the unique things you
这是你独特的事情之一
don't get with your regular monitoring
不能定期监控
tools what you can also use boss with
您还可以使用老板的工具
some caution if you include the spring
如果包括Spring ，请多加注意
cloud you get an environment endpoint
云你得到一个环境端点
you can post values to and change the
您可以将值过帐到并更改
current environment or even refresh the
当前环境甚至刷新
the application context and so you can
应用程序上下文，因此您可以
set here anything
在这里设置任何东西
and it will be applied to your spring
它将应用于您的春天
application but this is not persistent
应用程序，但这不是持久性的
when the application is going to restart
当应用程序将要重新启动时
all all is lost so it's good to try out
所有的一切都丢失了，所以尝试一下是个好习惯
things quickly but it's not so well
事情很快，但不是很好
suited for production for example yeah
例如适合生产
also we can see the active sprinkle
我们也可以看到主动洒
profiles up here yes we can't see all
这里的个人资料是的，我们看不到全部
instance here the beans we have a bean
实例这里的 bean 我们有一个 bean
endpoint so we can see the beans and
端点，以便我们可以看到Bean和
also what it depends on and which
还取决于什么
resource was I haven't stands the air
资源是我没有忍受
that this was being we can also see all
那就是我们也可以看到所有
our configuration property beans and in
我们的配置属性bean和
contrast to the environment and ions
与环境和离子形成对比
this has the benefit we also see the
这有好处，我们也看到了
default values the end the environment
默认值结束环境
endpoint would only show me the values
端点只会向我显示值
explicit ease explicitly set but if we
明确设置的明确难易程度，但如果我们
have some defaults and the configuration
有一些默认值和配置
properties I don't know yeah like the
我不知道的属性
endpoint path you also see the default
端点路径，您还会看到默认值
so you're really singing what what this
所以你真的在唱歌
property is bound again and even it's
属性再次被绑定，即使它是
the default we also have a view for
默认情况下，我们还有一个视图
showing the scheduled tasks yeah I told
显示预定的任务，是的，我告诉过
you about the watch tasks for these
您关于这些手表的任务
services we can see it here and how its
服务，我们可以在这里看到它，以及它如何
configured also useful the endpoint
配置对端点也有用
doesn't allow you to stop or pause the
不允许您停止或暂停
task so it's just view only for that I
任务，所以只为我查看
will switch the application
将切换应用程序
one of the first things we implemented
我们实施的第一件事
with promote admin was the longest
与促进管理员是最长的
endpoint and it's the one I love most I
端点，这是我最爱的端点
think you can switch logging levels at
认为您可以在以下位置切换日志记录级别
runtime you know either you believe me
运行时，您知道您是否相信我
or show you relax
或让你放松
[Music]
[音乐]
no follow so when I'm going to try it
没有跟随，所以当我要尝试时
for example yeah we see now we have a
例如，是的，我们现在看到了
lot of trace yeah you should be also a
是的，是的，你应该也是
bit cautious with that as having the
有点谨慎
root logger to trace
根记录器进行跟踪
might have some impact of your
可能会对您产生一些影响
performance or your log server is going
性能或您的日志服务器正在运行
to blow up I don't know
炸毁我不知道
and with the next version of Springwood
以及下一版的Springwood
admin we have some new feature here we
管理员，我们在这里有一些新功能
can now set the lock levels of all
现在可以设置所有的锁定级别
application at one time in the past you
过去一次申请
had to click through any instance of the
必须点击任何
application and now it's just one click
应用程序，现在只需单击一下
and there you go we have a log file
然后你有一个日志文件
endpoint for the log file view for the
日志文件视图的端点
log file endpoint itself the log file
日志文件端点本身是日志文件
endpoint requires you to write a file on
端点要求您在上写入文件
disk so that's what the log file Anton
磁盘，这就是日志文件Anton
just delivers this fire and which is not
只是提供这种火，而这不是
very well suited for cloud so I didn't
非常适合云计算，所以我没有
have done that I don't want to write a
做了我不想写的
file in my daugher container so that's
文件放在我的女儿容器中，所以
also a point where you might want to use
也是您可能想要使用的地方
some professional solution like an X tag
一些专业的解决方案，例如X标签
elasticsearch Cubana to do your lock
elasticsearch古巴做你的锁
management but if you have a smaller
管理，但如果您规模较小
setup of demoing things you may just
您可能只是演示示例的设置
have a power for your log file and can
对您的日志文件有能力，并且可以
easily watch the log file even with a
轻松查看日志文件，即使
follow function in the web UI
Web UI中的关注功能
[Music]
[音乐]
on my life earlier I had to drill a Kia
在我一生中，我不得不钻起亚
what do you know Jolokia okay Jolokia is
你知道Jolokia好吗Jolokia是
just a servlet delivering the Jaime
只是提供Jaime的servlet
expense via rest and you can interact
通过休息消费，您可以进行互动
with any Jay mix being via rest with
与任何Jay混搭都通过休息
Jolokia if you put the Jolokia call on
如果您拨打Jolokia，请致电Jolokia
your class pass or Springwood activator
您的课程准证或Springwood激活剂
will activate drill kia endpoint for you
将为您激活钻起亚端点
and it comes with great power but also
它具有强大的功能，但也
with great responsibility Springwood app
责任重大的Springwood应用程序
and provides a view you can see any
并提供一个您可以看到的视图
value you could even change the values
您甚至可以更改值
and work operations and yeah I don't
和工作操作，是的，我不
know if I use I just know now I stopped
知道我是否使用我只是知道现在我停了
my tomcat connector and my application
我的tomcat连接器和我的应用程序
is going to blow so yeah great power
会被打击，所以是强大的力量
great responsibilities but Jolokia have
责任重大，但乔洛基亚（Jolokia）有
a concepts of roles etc and you can
角色等的概念，您可以
restrict the access to Jay mix pins
限制对杰伊混音引脚的访问
I won't dive deeper into that but if you
我不会深入探讨，但是如果你
want to narrow things down and maybe
想缩小范围，也许
just have a read-only view you can
只要有一个只读视图就可以
configure it and the really nice thing
配置它和真正的好东西
about it if you have some dry mix pins
如果你有一些干混的别针
to reconfigure your application you have
重新配置您的应用程序
really an easy nice way to interact with
真的是一种轻松互动的好方法
them without having my remote method
他们没有我的远程方法
invocation tunneling to your container
调用隧道到您的容器
whatever yeah just use Springwood admin
是的，只要使用Springwood admin
and the trachea rest endpoint and
和气管其余端点和
everything is nice
一切都很好
yeah we have a view of the threats
是的，我们对威胁有看法
currently running in my application we
当前正在我的应用程序中运行
also can get some informations we just
也可以得到一些我们只是的信息
added this view after we had ourselves
我们拥有自己后添加了这种观点
some deadlocks and deadlocks
一些僵局和僵局
introduction and it was really a pain
介绍，真的很痛苦
for us to get the threat downs I don't
让我们摆脱威胁
know the nurse you can send it a secure
知道护士你可以寄给他一个安全的
signal and it will be spilled out of
信号，它会溢出来
your console but yeah it's really some
您的控制台，但是，确实是
time it's really hard to get an admin to
时间真的很难让管理员
do that for you if you are not allowed
如果不允许的话，为你做
and yeah so it's very easy to get to
是的，所以很容易到达
view the current state of stress also
查看当前的压力状态
which is very nice as there is a heap
这很好，因为有堆
dump endpoint in the activator and you
在激活器中转储端点，您
can just hit the button and download the
只需点击按钮并下载
endpoint be careful if you have a heap
端点要小心，如果有堆
of 10 gigabyte you were downloading a
您正在下载10 GB的磁盘
file of 10 gigabytes and also yeah there
10 GB的文件，也在那里
will maybe will be passwords and
可能是密码，
everything in this file I had a guy on
这个文件中的所有内容我都有一个家伙
the Springwood admin project or someone
Springwood管理项目或其他人
who brought an issue and appended a heap
谁带来了一个问题并附加了一个堆
dump on it no good idea so be careful
放弃它没有什么好主意，所以要小心
we're going to who were you given these
我们去找谁给你这些
files and also writing the heap tom when
文件并在以下情况下写入堆tom
I recall correctly it's the files first
我记得正确的是文件
written to disk and then delivered and
写入磁盘，然后交付并
yeah it's may harm your application yeah
是的，这可能会损害您的应用程序。
be careful if you have a web application
如果您有网络应用程序，请小心
we provide an a view for easily
我们提供了一个轻松的视图
seeing all your and mapped endpoints on
查看您所有的和映射的端点
servlets all filters so I use this a lot
servlets所有过滤器，所以我经常使用
when I'm calling services from other
当我打电话给其他人的服务时
teams and how was it called I don't know
团队，它怎么称呼我不知道
or maybe what do they offer the
也许他们提供什么
documentation really is sax so I hit
文档真的很萨克斯，所以我打
mappings and just watch okay what what
映射，然后就可以了
have them what would they have in place
请他们准备好他们准备的东西
we have we have an HTTP trace endpoint
我们有一个HTTP跟踪端点
I think I just need to hit the page
我想我只需要点击页面
[Music]
[音乐]
which shows you on all the last 100
向您显示最近的100个
requests of made to your HTTP server you
向您的HTTP服务器发出的请求
can see the headers for the recurrence
可以看到重复的标题
for the response
为了回应
some of the headers are not included
一些标题不包括在内
like authorization I think it's not a
像授权一样，我认为这不是
good idea to expose it this way and also
用这种方式暴露它的好主意
the bodies of the request response are
请求响应的主体是
not included as it would be too much
不包括在内，因为它将太多
data and for the upcoming Springwood 2.2
数据以及即将推出的Springwood 2.2
the HTTP present won't be active by
HTTP当前不会被激活
default they decided not to instantly at
默认情况下，他们决定不立即
the underlying a repository by default
默认情况下基础存储库
so if you want to use that instantly at
因此，如果您想立即使用
the instantiate and trace repository
实例化和跟踪存储库
currently they ship only an in-memory
目前他们只在内存中发货
solution and a spoon route will trace
解决方案和勺子路径将跟踪
you regressed made also on the web topic
您在网络主题上也做出了退步
is we provide a special and a view for
是我们提供了一个特殊的观点
the end points in the spring cloud
春天云的终点
gateway it was a community contribution
网关是社区的贡献
I don't use it myself
我自己不使用
you can delete routes at routes I don't
您可以删除我不选择的路线
know you have to write some ugly Jason
知道你必须写一些丑陋的杰森
in there so it's really for experts who
在那里，所以真的是给那些专家
knows what they are doing and we the
知道他们在做什么，我们
Springwood admin is looking at which
Springwood管理员正在查看哪个
actuator endpoint is expose and provides
执行器端点暴露并提供
a view so this gateway view is only
一个视图，因此此网关视图仅
shown for this application we have a
对于此应用程序，我们有一个
view for audit events with the audit
使用审核查看审核事件
event repository it's the same with the
事件存储库与
tracer repositories they decided not to
他们决定不使用的示踪剂库
ship it by default mostly it doesn't
默认情况下发货
make sense in this application mostly it
在这个应用程序中很有意义
makes sense if you have also also
如果你也有道理
security applied as for example
例如应用安全性
sprinkler spring security throws audit
洒水Spring 安全性引发审核
events for successful logins of failed
成功登录失败事件
logins and yeah you could also just look
登录，是的，你也可以看看
what what events happened here also one
这里发生了什么事也一
night also community contribution if
晚上还要社区贡献
you're using some spring cash compatible
您正在使用一些兼容的春季现金
cash like address r107 cash or eh cash
现金，如地址r107现金或eh现金
caffeine red earth and they're planning
咖啡因红土，他们正在计划
you get on cash endpoint which allows
您将获得现金端点
you to evict your cash and in the past
您驱逐现金和过去
we often just restarted our server
我们经常只是重启服务器
because it was the quickest thing to do
因为这是最快的事情
and now we can just hit the Clear button
现在我们可以点击清除按钮
and
和
everything is good okay um oh I'm
一切都很好，好吧，哦，我
running out of time okay let's do it a
时间用完了，好吧，让我们做一个
bit quicker that all the end point most
更快一点，所有终点
of them have shown and not mentioned fly
他们中有显示，没有提到苍蝇
oh really curry bears we can show you
哦，真的咖喱熊，我们可以告诉你
the status of your migrations we have a
您的迁移状态，我们有
sessions endpoint if you're using spring
会话终结点，如果您使用的是spring
sessions you can use this end point to
您可以使用此端点的会话
see all active sessions or even
查看所有活动会话，甚至
terminate the sessions if someone is
如果有人
behaving badly yeah
表现很差耶
as I mentioned we have a lot of
正如我提到的，我们有很多
notification options slack Microsoft
通知选项松弛Microsoft
teens blah blah blah blah most of them
青少年等等等等等等
are community contributions and our
是社区的贡献，我们的
configure configured by properties or no
配置按属性配置或否
need to code if you need some custom
如果需要一些自定义，则需要编码
things you can implement your own it's a
你可以自己实现的东西
very simple interface to implement yeah
非常简单的界面来实现
we have some advanced customizations I
我们有一些高级定制
would do it very quick I will put the
会很快完成的，我会把
code on github and we will make a treat
github上的代码，我们将请客
with a repository yeah if you for
有一个猫仓库，是的，如果您要
example I want to prevent that someone
我想防止那个人
is setting the root log level to trace
将根日志级别设置为要跟踪
you can write an instance exchange
你可以写一个实例交换
instance exchange filter function to to
实例交换过滤功能
intercept the request made from the
拦截来自
admin server to the actuator endpoints
管理服务器到执行器端点
and this for example just okay it's
例如，好吧，这是
supposed it's opposed to the loggers
认为它与记录器相反
endpoint oh the path ends with rude
终点哦，路径以粗鲁结尾
that's rude Laura
那是粗鲁的劳拉
oh no that's forbidden now and send
哦，不，现在禁止发送
status forbidden so if we do that on the
状态被禁止，所以如果我们在
URI I would get out of this Fayette yeah
我会从这个Fayette身上脱身的URI
that's very
那是非常
Castagnoli fire we just lock things to
Castagnoli开火，我们只是将事情锁定
disk to go to our log fire and spring
磁盘转到我们的日志火和春天
with edmund internally is using some
在内部使用edmund
kind of event sourcing so you can you
一种事件采购，所以您可以
get events for instance registered and
获取事件，例如注册并
points detected but also status downs
检测到点，但状态也会下降
that is up and that is that's what we
就是这样，这就是我们
are using for the slack notification
正在使用松弛通知
notification and we also provide some
通知，我们还提供了一些
modifiers which itself not really notify
本身并不真正通知的修饰符
but you can use them to filter
但您可以使用它们进行过滤
notifications like if you are no I'm
通知，如果你不，我是
going to update my applications I know
要更新我知道的应用程序
this application will go down yes set a
该应用程序将关闭是的设置一个
filter you can also do it by a rest
过滤你也可以休息一下
request so you could integrate it to
请求，因此您可以将其集成到
your delivery pipeline and set it up no
您的投放渠道并设置为否
sent send me no notifications and after
发送给我没有通知，之后
five minutes everything should be okay
五分钟，一切都会好起来的
now send me okay send me some
现在给我发送好吧，给我发送一些
notifications yeah and also we have a
通知是的，还有一个
notifier which bugs you over and over
通知者一遍又一遍地困扰您
again when the application is going down
当应用程序关闭时再次
you get a notification but if it doesn't
您会收到通知，但如果没有
come up you will be get a notification
上来您会收到通知
as well so you backed until it's
以及，所以你支持，直到
resolved yeah the Springwood admin
解决了，Springwood管理员
itself is using the view framework and
本身正在使用视图框架，
you can include your own views for
您可以包含自己的观点
custom endpoints when I shut the
自定义端点，当我关闭
application down in the beginning I just
我刚开始申请
used this endpoint it's really really
用了这个端点，真的
easy we have a read operation for the
容易，我们有一个读操作
status we have a write operation for the
状态，我们有一个写操作
status and this endpoint is also a
状态，该端点也是
health indicator so if we set this
健康指标，所以如果我们设置这个
status for example two out of service
状态，例如两个服务中断
the application is basically going down
该应用程序基本上已经关闭
and I've written also a small view for
而且我还为
that so I could do it with Bloomwood
这样我就可以用Bloomwood做到
admin I won't bother you with the
管理员，我不会打扰您的
build details but you have to add some
构建细节，但您必须添加一些
and PMB to your pond and we're using
和PMB到您的池塘，我们正在使用
view cui to build this we have sampled
查看cui以构建此示例
for that so you better just copy this
为此，您最好将其复制
code and on startup there is a global
代码，启动时有一个全局
variable you register an install
您注册安装的变量
callback which is used to to register
用于注册的回调
your custom view was a custom label and
您的自定义视图是一个自定义标签，
[Music]
[音乐]
this one yeah and just write it as a
这是的，只是将其写为
simple view component the view component
简单视图组件视图组件
itself will get the instance injected as
本身将实例注入为
property for which is currently shown
当前显示的属性
and on this instance we configure Axios
在此实例上，我们配置Axios
client to do the to interact with the
客户要做与之互动
actuator so it's just here if we click
执行器，如果我们单击，就在这里
this set status of the button we call
我们称为按钮的设置状态
the set status Metis method with which
设置状态Metis方法
is doing a post choose the activator
正在做一个职位，选择激活剂
endpoint and yeah basically when you
终结点，是的，基本上当你
built the application there are some CSS
内置应用程序有一些CSS
JavaScript under we are popping out at
我们下面的JavaScript出现在
the end put it in a special place on
最后把它放在一个特殊的地方
your class path for the admin server and
您的管理服务器的类路径，以及
it will show up as custom
它会显示为自定义
[Music]
[音乐]
custom view like this one and there okay
这样的自定义视图就可以了
that's basically it
基本上就是这样
we have a tag on Stack Overflow if you
如果您在堆栈溢出上有一个标签
have some suggestions suggestions find a
有一些建议，建议找到一个
back or anything else find an issue on
返回或其他任何问题
github or maybe you do a pull request
github或者也许你做一个pull请求
and yeah I will take some questions as
是的，我会问一些问题，
well sticky around for questions and if
很好地粘性问题，如果
you have questions tomorrow or on Monday
您明天或星期一有疑问
when you try everything at work I'm
当您尝试所有工作时，我
happy to chat with you on our Gator
很高兴在我们的鳄鱼上与您聊天
channel so I'm mostly on active there
频道，所以我主要是在那里活跃
thank you
谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]